brokeragentsocial.com 2012-05-03

# CrackerJack Agent - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Statement

CrackerJackAgent.com, LLC (we, us or CrackerJackAgent) has provided this Privacy Policy to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information that you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using the CrackerJackAgent web site located at www.CrackerJackAgent.com (the Web Site). 

**The information we collect**  
When you visit the Web Site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and Web Site use information collected by us as you browse our Web Site.

When you register on the Web Site, you create your own profile and privacy settings. Your profile includes various types of personal information, such as your personal interests, gender, age, education, and occupation. Your profile information, as well as your username and photo, may be displayed to other users of the Web Site. If you post personally identifiable information in areas of the site accessible to other users, you should be aware that such information can be read, collected, or used by other users, and could be used improperly (including for example to send you unsolicited messages). We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums or for others’ misuse of such information.

When you enter our Web Site, we collect the user’s browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all users of the Web Site and is used for administrative and analytical purposes, including diagnosing problems with our servers. In addition, when you enter our Web Site, we store certain information from your browser using “cookies.” A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use session cookies containing encrypted information to allow the system to uniquely identify you while you are logged in. This information allows us to process your online requests and preferences. We also use persistent cookies, that only we can read and use, for purposes of personal identification. We are careful about the security and confidentiality of the information stored in persistent cookies. For example, we do not store account numbers or passwords in persistent cookies. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature.

**Use of information obtained by CrackerJackAgent**  
We use personal information to provide the services we offer. Your profile, pictures and user name are displayed in order to facilitate user interaction and for purposes of our matching services. With the exception of inviting friends and certain notifications, a user’s email address is not shared or displayed. Users may communicate using various CrackerJackAgent messaging services, including a form of instant messenger, without disclosing their email addresses. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, CrackerJackAgent allows users to search for other members using certain profile matching systems and/or specific user names. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in the course of using the service provided by CrackerJackAgent and/or participating in any of the public forums available via the Web Site becomes public information; accordingly, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

From time to time, CrackerJackAgent or a partner, may sponsor a promotion or contest on the Web Site. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

In cases of suspected abuse or service problems, CrackerJackAgent may use an IP address in conjunction with other personally identifiable information to enforce our Terms of Service and/or to protect or troubleshoot this Web Site, its users or others who may be affected.

CrackerJackAgent may archive information, including personal information, you provide in the course of using our services and any other aspects of the CrackerJackAgent Web site. We store that information on servers that are controlled by us or by third parties who have agreed to comply with our commitments made under this Privacy Policy and with whom we have a contractual relationship. Archived information will not ordinarily be erased unless and until your entire account with CrackerJackAgent is deleted, and even then we may retain some or all of your information on back-up files; provided, however, we assume no obligation or guarantee to archive any information and do not warrant that any archived information will later be made available to you.

We may use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve the services we offer.

**Sharing your information with third parties**  
We may share demographic information with third parties, including companies with which we have a relationship. For example and without limitation:

We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as directing and displaying specific advertisements on the Web Site. In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use in connection with these business activities.

We may be required to disclose customer information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law or to protect our interests or property. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.

If the ownership of all or substantially all of the CrackerJackAgent business or assets were to change, your user information would likely be transferred to the new owner(s).

We may share with, or disclose or sell to third parties aggregated information. 

If you do not want to receive promotional email from CrackerJackAgent and/or do not want us to share your information with third parties for marketing purposes, please submit a request by emailing us using the contact link at the bottom of any of our web pages. We will make reasonable efforts to implement any choice you make as soon as possible; provided, however, CrackerJackAgent reserves the right to send you certain communications relating to the CrackerJackAgent service, such as service announcements and administrative messages without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

**Links**  
This site may contain links to other websites. CrackerJackAgent is not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to this Web Site.

**Third party advertising**  
Advertisements that appear on the Web Site are delivered to users by our advertising partners. Our advertising partners may download cookies to your computer. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement. In this way, they may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. This information allows an advertising network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. CrackerJackAgent does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by CrackerJackAgent and does not cover the use of cookies by any of its advertisers.

**Changing or removing information**  
CrackerJackAgent users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account. For technical reasons, any modifications or deletions which you request may take a short period of time to take effect.

If you change or delete any of your personal information, CrackerJackAgent will remove the old or deleted information from public view; however, as noted in Section 3 above, we may keep such information archived indefinitely.

**Security**  
CrackerJackAgent takes appropriate precautions to protect our users’ information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. Because email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. In addition, as all security measures are subject to possible circumvention, we cannot and do not provide any guarantees regarding the effectiveness of the security we employ or our ability to prevent third parties, acting unlawfully, from obtaining information that you provide to us. If you have any questions about the security of the CrackerJackAgent Web Site, please contact us.

CrackerJackAgent encourages all users to maintain a pseudonymous identity when using the services provided by CrackerJackAgent or any other public aspects of the Web Site. CrackerJackAgent cannot ensure that your identity, telephone number, work or home address and other personal identifying or contact information will not be discovered by other users of the Web Site. This is particularly true because your location (for example, within a radius of approximately five miles) will be revealed. It is, of course, more likely that your true identity will be discovered if you post photographs or share other unique identifying information about yourself on public areas of the Web Site.

**Changes in our privacy policy**  
We reserve the right to change our privacy policy at any time. If we do this, we will post the changes to this policy on this page and will indicate at the top of this page the policy’s effective date. We therefore encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy.

**Acceptance**  
This privacy policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms and conditions of CrackerJackAgent’s Terms of Service Agreement. Use of CrackerJackAgent’s services is subject to your compliance with those terms and conditions, which constitute a legal agreement between you and CrackerJackAgent. Each time you use CrackerJackAgent’s services you signify that you have read, understood and agree to be bound by the Terms of Service, which incorporates the privacy policy, and the applicable posted guidelines.

USE OF THIS WEBSITE SIGNIFIES THE ACCEPTANCE OF THE TERMS OF SERVICE AGREEMENT AND THE PRIVACY POLICY.

If you do not agree with the terms of either of these documents, please do not provide CrackerJackAgent with any information and do not use CrackerJackAgent’s services or this Web site. Your continued use of CrackerJackAgent’s services or this Web site in light of changes to this statement, to the privacy policy or to the relevant principles will signify your acceptance of the changes.

**Contacting CrackerJackAgent**  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us through the contact link at the bottom of any of our web pages.
